{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_La_Farge",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Peter La Farge's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9254263639450073,
            "question": "Is Peter La Farge associated with the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9083362817764282,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter La Farge's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9024882912635803,
            "question": "Is Peter La Farge originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.871506929397583,
            "question": "What country is considered Peter La Farge's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7103984355926514,
            "question": "Where was Peter La Farge from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.529932975769043,
            "question": "Where did Peter La Farge grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5006960034370422,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Peter La Farge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42957013845443726,
            "question": "Which nationality does Peter La Farge hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3813163936138153,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Peter La Farge's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28199389576911926,
            "question": "In what country did Peter La Farge spend his childhood?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter La Farge's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8928_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Peter La Farge's place of birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8928_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which nationality does Peter La Farge hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8928_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Peter La Farge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8928_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8928_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information about Peter La Farge, who was a New York-based folksinger. This implies that his hometown or at least significant part of his life was in the United States, supporting the statement that his hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}